<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drafts on Intellamech</title>
    <link>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drafts on Intellamech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.intellamech.com/draft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Title</title>
      <link>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/template_md_reveal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/template_md_reveal/</guid>
      <description>#
 This slideshow is written in Markdown, a plain text format.  view the slideshow in markdown  Converted into an HTML5 document using Pandoc. Pandoc uses a template to convert the Markdown to HTML5. The HTML5 document is automatically formatted for use with and linked to reveal.js by the template. Reveal is a feature-rich javascript library that displays the slideshow.  Yes, it really is that easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pandoc and Reveal</title>
      <link>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/pandoc_reveal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/pandoc_reveal/</guid>
      <description>#
##
 This slideshow is written in Markdown, a plain text format.  view the slideshow in markdown  Converted into an HTML5, revealjs document using Pandoc.  Yes, it really is that easy.
Aren&amp;rsquo;t some steps missing? Everything else just happens once you have it set up.
 Pandoc uses a template to convert the Markdown to HTML5. The HTML5 document is automatically formatted for use with and linked to reveal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Template</title>
      <link>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/template_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/template_project/</guid>
      <description>Project name Introduction Give your users an overview of the purpose and function of your project in a paragraph or two (at most). Because sometimes a picture is worth a thousand words, include screenshots when appropriate.
Usage Provide a short code snippet (if applicable), or short usage instructions
Contributing Give instructions on how to participate in your project patches.
Help Explain which communication channels are available to request help. Communication channels with a proven track record are mailing lists, IRC channels, and forums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rooting the Galaxy S2</title>
      <link>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/rooting_galaxy_s2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.intellamech.com/draft/rooting_galaxy_s2/</guid>
      <description> References  TUTORIAL How To Root the Sprint Galaxy S2 SPH-D710 How To Root the Sprint Galaxy S2 (SPH-D710) RWilco Files Samsung Epic 4G Touch guide to rooting How To Install A Custom Rom For Android Phones   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>